http://www.iit.edu/privacy

Skip to main site navigation
Skip to main content
Privacy Statement
This is a privacy statement for the website and pages of Illinois Institute of Technology (Illinois Tech). Illinois Tech is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit its web pages. This statement is intended to inform you concerning what information Illinois Tech collects while you browse our web pages, how we utilize this information and your options with respect to the same. The information disclosed in this statement is subject to change periodically in the sole discretion of Illinois Tech. Your continued use of our site implies your understanding and acceptance of this privacy statement.
Personally Identifying Information
As used in this statement, personally identifying information refers to any information that can be used to identify, contact or locate an individual, and may include such items as name, mailing or email addresses, or telephone number. Illinois Tech does not collect your personally identifying information when you visit our website unless you choose to provide such information to us; providing such information is strictly voluntary. Illinois Tech does not sell or rent to third parties personally identifying information submitted by visitors to our website, and we will not share such information with third parties (unless it is a subcontractor of Illinois Tech) except as required by law. We may share quantitative, non-personal data about our site visitors with affiliates, sponsors, institutional partners and other third parties.
Cookies
Like most websites, we use a feature of your browser to set a "cookie" on your computer. Cookies are small text files that reside on your computer and that identify you, anonymously, as a unique visitor. Our use of cookies does not reveal to us your personal information based solely on our use of the cookie. We use cookies to analyze traffic patterns and user interests, track user movement within our website, and gather broad demographic information (e.g., age and gender) for aggregate use for reporting purposes. Reputable web browsers will enable you to reject cookies or to choose which cookies you will accept. Please be advised that disabling cookies through your web browser may interfere with or prohibit your ability to enjoy the full functionality of our site.
Learn more about cookies and how you can disable them in your browser.
Google Analytics
We may use analytic tools such as Google Analytics to monitor and collect certain information about the use of this site, and to adjust our content to better serve the needs of the viewer. Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is subject to Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.
Third-Party Ad Networks, Remarketing and Behavioral Advertising
Although this website does not present advertising from third parties, we may participate in behavioral advertising of our own programs on other websites via digital advertising networks from Google, Facebook, LinkedIn and comparable services to create custom audiences for remarketing as well as to target similar audiences based on interests. This means that we may use cookies, pixel tags, analogous technologies, etc. from such networks to help measure ad performance (conversion tracking) and to identify you as having visited our website and other sites on the internet so that the networks can provide advertising about products and services tailored to your interests. If you would like to opt-out of third-party behavioral advertising that collects information on your use of this and other websites, you can do so by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative and the Digital Advertising Alliance.
Custom and Lookalike Audience (Facebook.com)
We may participate in Facebook.com's Custom and Lookalike Audience program which enables us to display personalized ads to persons on our email lists and persons who match like our current email lists when they visit Facebook.com. We provide Personal Information such as your email address and phone number to Facebook to enable Facebook to determine if you are a registered account holder with Facebook. You may opt-out of participation in our Facebook Custom Audience by sending an email, from the email address you are opting out of, to the email address marketing@iit.edu. For your opt-out to be effective, you must: (i) place the following text in the subject line of the email - "Opting Out of Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads", and (ii) in the body of the email, include your name and email address. We will forward your name and email address to Facebook.com with a request to delete you from all of our Facebook Custom Audience Ads.
Use of Links
Throughout our web pages we provide links to third-party websites which may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for, and exercise no control over, these organizations, their views, their technology or the accuracy of the information contained on these other websites.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us at webmaster@iit.edu.
Effective June 2018
Learn more...
Illinois Tech welcomes you to join our community of people who discover, create, and solve. Apply today, visit us in Chicago, and contact us for more information.
Request Info
Visit
Apply
